const monthsToNumbers = [
    {
        question: 'Styczeń',
        answers: ['1'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Luty',
        answers: ['2'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Marzec',
        answers: ['3'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Kwiecień',
        answers: ['4'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Maj',
        answers: ['5'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Czerwiec',
        answers: ['6'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Lipiec',
        answers: ['7'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Sierpień',
        answers: ['8'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Wrzesień',
        answers: ['9'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Październik',
        answers: ['10'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Listopad',
        answers: ['11'],
    },
    {
        question: 'Grudzień',
        answers: ['12'],
    },
];

export default monthsToNumbers;
